There is a brother there that the wife is planning to leave him now.
Come on.
Why does your wife want to leave you?
She is there.
Why do you want to leave your husband?
I'm no more feeling okay.
You don't have feelings.
Come here.
It is not that you don't have feelings.
Come on.
Come here!
She told you that she wants to leave you?
Yes.
Already for the past months, she
has not been sleeping with you.
Yes, sir. I don't sleep with him any longer.
You don't sleep with him?
Yes.
You sleep in your room separately.
She has removed the ring.
You have removed the ring?
Yes.
After the deliverance, she will now see the potential in you.
Come on!
Don't worry, she will see the good in you.
The good in you - she could not
see it again because she was possessed
Come on. See this man.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
It's alright.
Thank You, Jesus!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Let's clap for Jesus!
Clap for Jesus once again!
Remember, Jesus has come to restore relationship.
Jesus has come to put an end to the past and give birth to the future.
Give thanks to Him.
Viewers all over the world, as you are watching, remember,
Jesus is the same yesterday, today and forever.
And as the man of God says:
In a Christian home, misunderstanding leads to greater understanding.
So whatever challenges you are facing, listen to this testimony.
You will know that there is a way where there seems to be no way.
The way is Jesus Christ!
Give thanks to Him once again.
Hallelujah!
We are seeing you joyful because the Lord has done something in your life.
Hallelujah. Can you please introduce yourselves to our viewers
and tell us the testimony, what Jesus
has done in your life,
in your marital life, in Jesus' name.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I'm so glad this morning.
My name is Mrs Esabella Samtu from Togo.
The man beside me is my husband.
What brought us to The SCOAN was a marital problem.
Last week, the man of God prophesied,
telling us that there was a man over there whose wife wanted to divorce him.
He said that I took off my ring and that I had not slept with him for a long time.
He also said I moved into my room.
I confirm today that the prophecy is hundred percent true.
He prayed with us and cast away the spirit.
It is almost six years that I have been married to my husband.
He did everything a man can do for a woman to be happy, yet I had no affection for him.
I heard that when I wanted to divorce him, he went and took some drugs to kill himself.
We got scared of the whole thing and rushed to God.
God has opened His hands to us and put a smile on our faces.
We are so happy.
Mrs Esabella Samtu & Husband
Prophecy Testimony
Anytime he slept with me, I didn't like it; I didn't feel him.
There was a time he came to my office and I introduced him as my brother.
I was not proud of him as a man besides me.
I even planned to go to another man, and I had packed my things.
I had hoped that when we came to The SCOAN,
the man of God would say that he was not good for me.
Then, I would go and take my things out.
He was praying that God should restore his marriage because God had me for him.
He was eager to do everything a man could do to keep his marriage.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
You said you had taken off the wedding rings. Tell us much more about that.
For about six months, I was not wearing the wedding rings.
I kept them somewhere else.
But that day - last week Sunday - I just asked for it when the spirit was out of me.
I went for it myself and wore it.
is when that
thing happened before I realized
It is then that I realised that this man is good for me.
He has so much potential in him.
Clap for Jesus!
Madam, tell us what are the changes you observed in your relationship
with your husband since that deliverance.
Oh, so good ones.
When we met as husband and wife, I realised there was a change;
I liked it so much.
Mrs Esabella Samtu & Husband
Prophecy Testimony
Before, I didn't like holding him while we were walking but right now, I can hold him.
I can kiss him and do everything with him.
I'm proud to have him as my husband.
Thank you!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus! Clap for Jesus!
Let someone say, "A new love has come.
A new understanding has come".
Who can justly do it?
- Jesus Christ, the Restorer.
Clap for Him once again.
Madam, there are many couples that are watching you right now all over the world,
who are going through the tough situation you went through.
What is your advice to them?
I would like to tell the whole world,
especially couples who are in the same situation as we were before,
not to take decisions on their own.
They should seek the face of God.
God is capable of solving the problem and put a smile on their face.
Amen.
Clap for Jesus Christ!
Sir, we are seeing you smiling. Tell us what God has done for you.
We want to hear from you your experience.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I give thanks to God for the life of Prophet T.B. Joshua, who allowed us to have joy today.
We came to the arena of liberty because we were having marital problems.
Some months ago, my wife decided to leave me.
There were different reasons for that decision.
First of all, she said she would leave me because she needed to have children.
She would say she had no feelings for me and that she felt oppressed; so, I should let her go.
I was confused and did not know who to confide in or where to find solution to the problem.
He is thanking God for the life of Prophet T.B. Joshua, for what God has done in his life.
The problem that brought him was a marital problem.
For a long time, there was no affection
and his wife told him that she wanted to leave him for many reasons.
First, they have no child and second, no affection in the relationship.
So, I was praying and I also consulted my two pastor friends who advised me.
He told me that he knew one place, the arena of liberty where I would find solution.
So, I decided to come to the arena of liberty.
Before we came, my wife had already removed her wedding ring but I brought it with me.
On Sunday, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied that there was a man whose wife wanted to leave him.
Immediately we came forward, the man of God prayed for us and we were delivered.
I want to ask you a question.
He said that when the problem became so tough,
they decided to come to the arena of liberty to seek the face of God.
The wife had removed the ring already,
meaning she had already taken the decision to leave him.
So when they came here to the church of God, the man of God gave a word of prophecy,
fetched them out and exposed the root cause of their problem.
After the word of prophecy, they were delivered and restored.
I want to ask you one question.
When your wife removed the ring, what came to your mind?
I came seeking God at the arena of liberty and I found solution. I confirm that God is here.
He said he was so confused - how can God unsettle a marriage
where the wife is praying for separation, and the husband is praying for restoration.
So they decided to come to the arena of liberty to seek the truth - the face of God.
He wants to tell everybody that God is alive and God is real.
Mrs Esabella Samtu & Husband
Prophecy Testimony
After the deliverance, I feel happy and sleep like a new-born baby.
He says he is very happy and sleeps like
a baby.
God has restored their marriage and they are happy and give thanks to God
for the mighty works He has done through the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Many married men are having trouble.
Please, what is your advice to those watching you?
To every man in that same situation,
I advise them to be patient, pray and seek the face of God.
Only God has the solution to all fundamental issues of life.
He says that it is only God who has the answer to all your troubles.
Please don't listen to advice of people around you.
Don't take your own decision; come and seek the face of God.
When God comes, solution comes, in Jesus' name.
Let's clap for Jesus once again.
Madam, we want to hear your advice to all the people watching all over the world.
To the women, the wives that are having trouble in their marital life -
what is your advice to them?
I would like to tell all couples to always seek the face of God
before taking any kind of decision, no matter the situation.
Thank you!
Let's clap for Jesus Christ.
Let's clap for Him.
Mrs Esabella Samtu & Husband
Prophecy Testimony
Thank You, Jesus.
TT: lizz ndung'u 03/09/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 26/09/2018